rpxnow.com 2013-05-07

# Janrain: User management platform for the social web

## Janrain Privacy Policy

Welcome to Janrain Engage, the simple, consistent, secure authentication and data portability service. We take your privacy seriously; therefore, below we provide you with our privacy policy, where we intend to be transparent about any information we collect, how we intend to use it to your benefit, and what choices you have when you register with us and use Janrain Engage. 

### Here are our commitments

  * Your privacy remains strictly under your control
  * The privacy of state data from your end users remains strictly under your control
  * You can end your account at any time
  * We will never disclose your personally-identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes unless you expressly tell us to 
  * You can decide whether you want to receive any offers from us that may be of interest to you

### Information Practices

When you register and use Janrain Engage, you provide information to us. When Janrain Engage is being used by your web site, additional state data is retained as a result of authentication and data flow from provider. 

In the following three sections, we explain what information is collected, how it is used to your benefit, and the choices that you have with your information. 

### Information Collected by Janrain

Depending on how you interact with Janrain Engage, you provide us with information, which may include: (a) site name, email address, and other registration information; (b) your interaction with Janrain Engage features and advertisements; (c) transaction-related information, such as, when you download software from us; and (d) information you provide us when you contact us for help. As part of your personal profile, you may choose to submit additional information. 

State data is often collected from providers during the normal operation of the Janrain Engage service. This data ranges in content and policy depending on nature of the endpoints. This data is kept persistantly by Janrain only to perform authentication and data services. This data is held on behalf of the you, and made available at your request. 

We also collect other non-personally identifiable data, which may include your IP address and what browser you are using so that we can improve Janrain's services for you. 

### Use of Information

If provided, we will use your email address to contact you from time to time and we will use your email address for security reasons to confirm that you are who you say you are. You can control the types and frequencies of certain emails you receive, although you agree that we may always contact you to provide you with important information or required notices required by Janrain. 

We may use your information (a) to deliver the Janrain services and features desired by you (including any customization features requested by you), (b) to improve our services to you, (c) to personalize content and offers that may be of interest to you, (d) to respond to your inquiries, and (e) to fulfill your request for products or services. 

We may use the non-personally identifiable information, like your IP address, to statistically analyze site usage and to customize our site's content, layout and services. The resulting information will allow us to improve our services and better understand and serve our users. 

We do not sell customer lists. We will not share any information that identifies you personally with any third party for marketing purposes. We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect our rights and property or the rights and property of the public. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency in doing so. 

### Minors

Children under the age of thirteen (13) are not eligible to use our service and must not submit any personal information to us. 

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of Janrain Engage if you do so. 

### Security

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account. Please do not disclose your login credentials to unauthorized people. We use industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us at privacy@janrain.com. 

### Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of this website or our service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy. 

### Canceling Your Account

You always have the option to cancel using the service at any time. 

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about Janrain's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at this email address: privacy@janrain.com
